cafepharma.com 2014-12-17

# Privacy Policy | Cafepharma

**Introduction**

Your privacy is very important to us. We are Cafepharma, Inc. (a Georgia corporation),  
and we post this Privacy Policy so that you are aware of the information we collect, how it is handled, and with whom it is shared. If you need to contact us, please do so here.

The cafepharma sites are web sites under Cafepharma’s control. The cafepharma sites include a variety of features and services, including an on-line service to post and search employment opportunities. The cafepharma sites also include on-line communities  
designed to facilitate valuable professional and personal networking among users based on common experiences and interests, and allow you to create individual profiles (and a “Profile Name”), which may include personal information (“Profiles”).

Protect your personal information by never providing social security, credit card, or bank account numbers to other parties.

Please note that when you link to sites from cafepharma sites, this Privacy Policy does not apply, and we cannot control the activities on those other sites.

**Who And What Are Not Covered By This Privacy Policy**

You must be 13 years of age, or older, to visit or use any cafepharma site in any manner,  
and if under the age of 18 (or the age of majority as that is defined in your jurisdiction), you must use cafepharma sites under the supervision of a parent, legal guardian, or other responsible adult.

If any of our sites deal with information not specifically mentioned in this Policy, then  
such information is not covered by this Policy. For example, this Policy does not cover data that we collect offline, on businesses or legal entities, on our employees, or through other third-party sites.

Please realize that personal information you submit through resumes, or other uploaded or transmitted documents, is also not subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Information You Provide To Us**

Unless we otherwise described a situation about gathering information from you in this Policy, it will be obvious to you that you are providing information (as we generally seek only to collect personal information that you provide on a voluntary basis).

You are allowed to use many features of cafepharma sites without any ‘registration’ or providing of any information, and therefore use such features anonymously. For example, our message boards in the forums.

Please understand that even when using the site anonymously, your web browser or client software may transmit certain geographic information, or information regarding your choices while on our websites.

For some activities, we may ask you to create a username and password, supply us with a valid e-mail address, and allow you to provide associated personal and non- personal information and a link to your website. For some other activities, we may ask  
you for additional personal and non-personal information. Either set of information is considered “Bio Information.”

We use “cookies” (small pieces of data stored for an extended period of time on your computer, mobile phone, or other device) for individual sessions when you visit the site, in order to facilitate your use of the website. We use such “session cookies” for both  
anonymous and logged-in users. These session cookies, however, cannot be used to determine a visitor’s actions on our web sites, and we do not use ‘third party tracking’ cookies to track your actions on our or other sites.

We do not collect IP addresses of anonymous users, and seek to prevent our ability to determine whom you are when you post anonymously, or your exact location.

**Information You Provide Others Through Our Site**

A primary purpose of our site is to allow you to share information with others, including your opinions, facts about your workplace, and facts about yourself. Please be aware that others may use such information to identify you, despite your anonymous posting of such information.

When posting under a Profile Name, an option allows others to see all your posts in the aggregate, or see a listing of all posts made under such Profile Name. Visitors to our site can also access and see the Bio Information that you choose to provide when you create  
your Profile.

If you do not want us to store metadata associated with content that you share on our sites (such as photos), please remove the metadata before uploading the content.

Sometimes the advertisers who present ads on our sites use technological methods to measure the effectiveness of their ads, and to personalize advertising content. You may use your browser cookie settings to limit or prevent the placement of cookies  
by advertising networks. We do not share personally identifiable information with advertisers.

**Situations In Which We Share Your Information With Others**

We may share your information with third parties if we believe the sharing is permitted by you, reasonably necessary to offer our services, or when legally required to do so. We highly regard your privacy, and will not share your information except as detailed here.

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Again, we view protection of users' privacy as a very important community principle.

We may disclose information pursuant to subpoenas, court orders, or other requests (including criminal and civil matters) if we have a good faith belief that the law requires the response. We may also share information when we have a good faith belief it is  
necessary to prevent threats against our web services, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts, or other government entities.

**Again, however, we do not keep any information on visitors except as expressly detailed in this Policy, and therefore have little-to-no information to share regarding anonymous postings.**

If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes, we may transfer any information we may have to the new owner so that the service can continue to operate. In such a case, your information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-  
existing Privacy Policy.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use your information to offer our services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features, and to supply you with customer support. We may contact you with service-related announcements from time to time.

We look to detect and address anomalous activity that is an abuse of our system, or illegal. These efforts may on occasion result in a temporary or permanent suspension, or termination of some functions for some users.

Again, your web browser or client software may transmit certain geographic information, or information regarding your choices while on our websites. We may use this information, and other information that you provide us, to generate aggregate statistics about our user community, and may provide such information to advertisers and our  
partners. In addition, we may use such information for site security or system integrity (the prevention of hacking, bots, spiders, etc.).

We may monitor use of the products and services on this site, and use such information for internal business purposes, or in accordance with the rules of any applicable regulatory, or self-regulatory organization. We reserve the right to offer third party services and products to you based on the preferences that you identify, and such offers  
may be made by us, or by third parties.

As a convenience to you, Cafepharma may provide links on this site to websites operated by other persons and entities.

**Security of Data**

Cafepharma makes no representation regarding the security of this site, including with respect to the ability of unauthorized persons to intercept or access information transmitted by you through this site.

While we take steps to limit access to your information, please be aware that such steps are not perfect, and we cannot insure that the information you share with us will not become publicly available.

We store and process your information on computers located in the United States that are protected by physical as well as technological security devices. You can access and modify the information you provide us and choose not to receive certain communications  
by signing-in to your account.

**Other Terms**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we may notify you here, by means of a notice on our home page, another appropriate location, or by email.

If you ever remove information from your profile, or modify your postings, copies of that information may still remain accessible through third-party platforms through the use of caches, or other methods.

International users: This site is controlled, operated and administered by Cafepharma and its service provider from offices within the United States of America. Cafepharma makes no representation, except as expressly otherwise  
provided in writing to you, that materials on this site are appropriate or available for use at other locations outside of the United States, and access to them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited. If you access this site from  
locations outside of the United States of America, then you are responsible to insure that it complies with all local laws. These Terms of Use will be governed by the laws of the state of Georgia, U.S.A. without regard to conflict of laws provisions, or  
principles.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 4, 2011.
